Gabrielle Giffords Papers, 1995-2012 (bulk 2007-2012)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Subgroup II: Media Files, 2005-2012
  - Series 2: Audio Visual Materials, 2005-2012
    - Subseries 1: Video cassettes, 2007-2010
      - Arizona Illustrated, Tony Paniagua - RT: Gabrielle Giffords, Arizona Public Media, 2010 (Box 45, Folder 1)
      - Fox 11 9 PM- Gaza Escape, August 20, 2007 (Box 45, Folder 2)
      - Representative Giffords Statement 3:31 (Access copy available), December 4, 2007 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Subseries 2: Compact Discs, 2005-2012
      This subseries contains CDs and DVDs of audio and visual materials such as floor statements, town hall recordings and interviews as well as electronic files on CD including photographs especially from congressional delegation trips. Some documents such as presentations and other documents are also included.
      - Giffords, May 22 (Box 45, Folder 4)
      - Journal of the US House of Representatives 109th Congress First Session, 2005 (Box 45, Folder 5)
      - Iraq/Israel Photos from Gabrielle Giffords, February 2007 (Box 45, Folder 6)
      - US House of Representatives House Recording Studio Congresswoman Giffords NPR radio interview with Peter Roskam, February 15, 2007 (Box 45, Folder 7)
      - US House of Representatives House Recording Studio Rep. Giffords VTC Immigration-Border Security Teleconference with Sheriffs (52:00:13)(DVD), March 15, 2007 (Box 45, Folder 8)
      - Immigration Reform Hearings Pima College Tucson Congresswoman Gabrielle Giffords, April 4, 2007 (Box 45, Folder 9)
      - The USDA Forest Service Presents The Bud Gode Trail Opening Ceremony at Madera Canyon, October 13, 2007 (Box 45, Folder 10)
      - The USDA Forest Service Presents The Bud Gode Trail Opening Ceremony at Madera Canyon, October 13, 2007 (Box 45, Folder 11)
      - US House of Representatives House Recording Studio Rep. Giffords Greeting (7:17) (DVD), October 25, 2007 (Box 45, Folder 12)
      - Rep. Giffords visits Nogales BP Station, November 18, 2007 (Box 45, Folder 13)
      - Congresswoman Gabrielle Giffords visits Breault Research, November 28, 2007 (Box 45, Folder 14)
      - Cox Votes: Congresswoman Gabrielle Giffords Forum photos from visit to Cox Communications, November 29, 2007 (Box 45, Folder 15)
      - Giffords C ITDC-CEAC, November 29, 2007 (Box 45, Folder 16)
      - Congressional visit Fort Huachuca US Army photos, November, 2007 (Box 45, Folder 17)
      - Skelton (Armed Services Committee Chairman visit to DM and Fort Huachuca), November, 2007 (Box 45, Folder 18)
      - Smith Iraq Codel Disk 3 movies, November, 2007 (Box 45, Folder 19)
      - News Clips and Floor Speeches 1387-1954 Gabby 2007 Disc 2 (Box 45, Folder 20)
      - News Clips and Floor Speeches 1961-2352 Gabby 2007 Disc 3 (Box 45, Folder 21)
      - Gabrielle Giffords Tucson Nursery- David Bean Photography, January 18, 2008 (Box 45, Folder 22)
      - DFA's meeting with Giffords Chief of Staff, Maura Policelli, February 20, 2008 (Box 45, Folder 23)
      - Impeachment Forum 10 and 60 min versions from Google and YouTube, February 20, 2008 (Box 45, Folder 24)
      - Mark and Gabrielle photos from the Malpai Border Mule Ride, February 24, 2008 (Box 45, Folder 25)
      - Pepper Viner CNR Green Expo, March 1, 2008-March 2, 2008 (Box 45, Folder 26)
      - GG in S+T Hearing, March 5, 2008 (Box 45, Folder 27)
      - Giffords Safeway Ina and Oracle; Photos by Scott Taras. All photos (246) and 26 photos that are toned, sharpened and free of dust from my sensor, March 15, 2008 (Box 45, Folder 28)
      - Safeway at Ina and Oracle Photos by Scott A Taras, March 15, 2008 (Box 45, Folder 29)
      - SRP PIC Luncheon Speech by Rep. Gabrielle Giffords (14:00), March 19, 2008 (Box 45, Folder 30)
      - G.G. WM E-Verify, May 5, 2008 (Box 45, Folder 31)
      - US House of Representatives House Recording Studio Ways and Mean Committee R&R 662 (DVD), May 6, 2008 (Box 45, Folder 32)
      - GG Armed Services, May 14, 2008 (Box 45, Folder 33)
      - US House of Representatives House Recording Studio Rep. Giffords VTC (1:28:00) (Windows Media Video 320x240@282), July 8, 2008 (Box 45, Folder 34)
      - US House of Representatives House Recording Studio Rep. Giffords VTC (1:20) (DVD), July 9, 2008 (Box 45, Folder 35)
      - Water Amendment Giffords, July 16, 2008 (Box 45, Folder 36)
      - Congresswomans Giffords trip to AGM, July 18, 2008 (Box 45, Folder 37)
      - Making Big Solar Work, National Academies, July 29, 2008 (Box 45, Folder 38)
      - Gabby Giffords, Daniel Snyder for Military spouse mal, August 12, 2008 (Box 45, Folder 39)
      - Gabrielle Giffords Health Effect of Climate Change, November 6, 2008 (Box 45, Folder 40)
      - Giffords for Congress Election night-Chris Richards, 2008 (Box 45, Folder 41)
      - Giffords for Congress Election night photos by Caryn Schenewenke, 2008 (Box 45, Folder 42)
      - Giffords for Congress professional campaign photos- 1, 2008 (Box 45, Folder 43)
      - US House of Representatives House Recording Studio Rep. Giffords Statement (10:28) (DVD), January 7, 2009 (Box 45, Folder 44)
      - US House of Representatives House Recording Studio VTC (Windows Media 640x480@764) (CD), February 18, 2009 (Box 45, Folder 45)
      - US House of Representatives House Recording Studio Committee on Budget Rep. Giffords (6:30) (DVD), March 11, 2009 (Box 45, Folder 46)
      - US House of Representatives House Recording Studio Committee on Budget Rep. Giffords (6:30) (wmv 320x240@282), March 11, 2009 (Box 45, Folder 47)
      - US House of Representatives House Recording Studio Rep. Giffords (2:50) (Windows Media 320x240@282), March 23, 2009 (Box 45, Folder 48)
      - Healthcare Town Hall with Gabrielle Giffords, May 26, 2009 (Box 45, Folder 49)
      - US House of Representatives House Recording Studio Rep. Giffords Statement 1 (:30), Statement 2 (1:51) (Windows Media 320x240@282 CD), June 10, 2009 (Box 45, Folder 50)
      - US House of Representatives House Recording Studio Rep. Giffords Statement (4:50) (DVD), June 24, 2009 (Box 45, Folder 51)
      - US House of Representatives House Recording Studio Rep. Giffords (4:50) (CD Windows Media 320x@293), June 24, 2009 (Box 45, Folder 52)
      - Congresswoman Gabrielle Giffords visit to Luke AFB, August 1, 2009 (Box 45, Folder 53)
      - NGAUS conference Nashville, TN Rep. Giffords appears halfway through, September 12, 2009 (Box 45, Folder 54)
      - US House of Representatives House Recording Studio Rep. Giffords Greeting Insurance Reform-Health Insurance (3:41) (DVD), Septemeber 17, 2009 (Box 45, Folder 55)
      - Rosemont Mine visit DVD; Giffords, Jensen,:Elgin, GV and Mine site, October 22, 2009 (Box 45, Folder 56)
      - Gabrielle Giffords photos from Udall event. Polixenni Photography, November 13, 2009 (Box 45, Folder 57)
      - Stewart L Udall event video, November 13, 2009 (Box 45, Folder 58)
      - US House of Representatives House Recording Studio Rep. Giffords (:56) (Windows Media 640x480 CD), December 16, 2009 (Box 45, Folder 59)
      - Codel Smith Israel, Lebannon, Syria, Kuwait, Iraq, Belgium, 2009 (Box 45, Folder 60)
      - Codel Smith- Regional Command-East (RC-E) CJTF-101, 2009 (Box 45, Folder 61)
      - National Guard Association Charles S. Dick Award 2009 (DVD) (Box 45, Folder 62)
      - US House of Representatives House Recording Studio Rep. Giffords Statement 20th Century Career Workshop and Expo (2:48) (AVI 720x480 CD), January 13, 2010 (Box 45, Folder 63)
      - Statement, January 20, 2010 (Box 45, Folder 64)
      - US House of Representatives House Recording Studio Rep. Giffords Statement (MPG) (4:55) (CD), March 3, 2010 (Box 45, Folder 65)
      - Giffords rancher meeting and press conference at Apache Elementary School "Murder and Aftermath Border Violence in America", March 31, 2010 (Box 45, Folder 66)
      - US House of Representatives House Recording Studio Rep. Giffords 100 Anniversary of Iron Workers Local 75 message (01:11) (Windows Media Video 640x480@452k CD), May 28, 2010 (Box 45, Folder 67)
      - Congresswoman Giffords Federal Issues Luncheon video, July 8, 2010 (Box 45, Folder 68)
      - Congresswoman Giffords Rep. Thompson Rancher Town Hall video, July 9, 2010 (Box 45, Folder 69)
      - Congresswoman Giffords Rep. Thompson visit to AZ photos, July, 2010 (Box 45, Folder 70)
      - Congresswoman Giffords Rep. Thompson visit to AZ photos, July, 2010 (Box 45, Folder 71)
      - Congresswoman Giffords Dr. Westphal visit to AZ photos, July, 2010 (Box 45, Folder 72)
      - Rep. Gabrielle Giffords and US Under Secretary of the Army Dr. Joseph Westphal visiting Raytheon, July 12, 2010 (Box 45, Folder 73)
      - Congresswoman Gabrielle Giffords photo slideshow DVD 2010- Year in Review, December, 2010 (Box 45, Folder 74)
      - Photos slideshow DVD Congresswoman Gabrielle Giffords 2010: Year in Review, December, 2010 (Box 45, Folder 75)
      - Gabby 40th B-Day photos slideshow, 2010 (Box 45, Folder 76)
      - White House Photos President Obama and memorial, January 12, 2011 (Box 45, Folder 77)
      - NBC Nightly News with Brian Williams and Today; Captain Mark Kelly with Brian Williams, February 14, 2011 (Box 45, Folder 78)
      - "Get Well Greetings from the Women's Caucus" Windows Media File (16:45), February 14, 2011 (Box 45, Folder 79)
      - All solar folder from SARA, February, 2011 (Box 45, Folder 80)
      - Border Tour 399 photos taken by Stephanie Coronado, May 22, 2011 (Box 45, Folder 81)
      - Rep. Gabrielle Giffords web site files archived, January 26, 2012 (Box 45, Folder 82)
      - Arizona Illustrated Representative Gabrielle Giffords, undated (Box 45, Folder 83)
      - Congresswoman Giffords visits VA Hospital KVOA and KGUN 5 PM news, KVOA and KGUN 10 PM late news, undated (Box 45, Folder 84)
      - Congresswoman Gabrielle Giffords 8th District of Arizona, undated (Box 45, Folder 85)
      - Courthouse, undated (Box 45, Folder 86)
      - EFRC press conference, undated (Box 45, Folder 87)
      - La Frontera Gabrielle Giffords, undated (Box 45, Folder 88)
      - Giffords at Davis Monthan, undated (Box 45, Folder 89)
      - Giffords @ Davis Monthan Hi Res, undated (Box 45, Folder 90)
      - Giffords Interview, undated (Box 45, Folder 91)
      - Giffords NASA 50, undated (Box 45, Folder 92)
      - Giffords Office from KVOA, undated (Box 45, Folder 93)
      - Gila River Indian Community, undated (Box 45, Folder 94)
      - NARAL Pro-Choice America- Rep. Giffords DVD, undated (Box 45, Folder 95)
      - Tucson Nursery, Wienermobile, Santa 2006, Santa 2007- David Bean Photography, undated (Box 45, Folder 96)
  - Series 3: Memorabilia, 2006-2011
    This series contains plaques, awards and certificates from Giffords’ congressional career. Also included are guest books, campaign banners and NASA collages.
    - Award, Beacon of Courage & Dedication, 8th Annual World Congress of the International Brain Mapping & Intraoperative Surgical Planning Society, June 8, 2011-June 10, 2011 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Award, Pioneer in Healthcare Policy, 8th Annual World Congress of the International Brain Mapping & Intraoperative Surgical Planning Society, June 8, 2011-June 10, 2011 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Banner: Giffords Campaign, tan, undated (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Banner: Giffords Campaign, white, undated (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Bill: S. 39- Bennett Freeze, 2009 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Business card, undated (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Certificates, 2006-2010 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Collage: National Aeronautics and Space Administration, STS-118, August 8, 2007-August 21, 2007 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Collage: National Aeronautics and Space Administration, STS-119, March 15, 2009-March 28, 2009 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Collage: National Aeronautics and Space Administration, STS-127, July 15, 2009-July 31, 2009 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Collage: National Aeronautics and Space Administration, STS-128, August 28, 2009-11-Sep-09 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Ephemera: Giffords for United States Senate bumper sticker, undated (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Ephemera: National Aeronautics and Space Administration buttons, undated (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Event sign-in sheets, 2011 (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Flag: Operation Enduring Freedom support, January 11, 2011 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Identification Card: 110th Congress, 2007-2009 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Office sign-in sheets, 2010-2011 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Plaque: 2011 Community Champion, October 11, 2011 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Plaque: Floor Statement, Honoring the Outstanding Service of the 354th Expeditionary Fighter Squadron, January 21, 2010 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Plaque: Floor Statement, Honoring the Service and Sacrifice of United States Army Sergeant First Class James E. Thode, December 9, 2010 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Poster: Crossroads at Silverbell Park, February 27, 2010 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Poster: District 8 final results (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Poster: Gabrielle Giffords Family Assistance Center visualization and layout, undated (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Poster: Giffords for Congress Go Vote 2008 Concert (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Sign: Congressional plaque, undated (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Events: United States Army Intelligence and Security Command visit to the United States Army Intelligence & Security Command, October 18, 2008 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Photographs: Freshman class, 2006 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Photographs: Multi-National Security Transition Command, Iraq and North Atlantic Treaty Organization-Training Mission, Iraq, undated (Box 49, Folder 8)
- Subgroup III: January 8, 2011 Tucson, Arizona shooting, 2011-2012
  This subgroup contains materials related to the shooting at Giffords’ “Congress on your Corner” event that killed six including Giffords’ congressional staffer Gabriel Zimmerman and injured 13. Gabrielle Giffords was shot in the head but survived. The bulk of the materials came from her district and congressional office. Included are well wishes, press clippings and memorabilia. For additional materials related to the January 8th memorials please contact Tucson’s January 8 Memorial Foundation.
  - Series 1: Correspondence, 2011
    This series contains correspondence, primarily cards and letters sent by the public to Giffords after the shooting. Also included are well wishes from public figures as well as cards to other victims, primarily Gabe Zimmerman’s family. Well wishes to Giffords were sampled.
    - Well wishes (1 of 62), January, 2011 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Well wishes (2 of 62), January, 2011 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Well wishes (3 of 62), January, 2011 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Well wishes (4 of 62), January, 2011 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Well wishes (5 of 62), January, 2011 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Well wishes (6 of 62), January, 2011 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Well wishes (7 of 62), January, 2011 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Well wishes (8 of 62), January, 2011 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Well wishes (9 of 62), January, 2011 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Well wishes (10 of 62), January, 2011 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Well wishes (11 of 62), January, 2011 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Well wishes (12 of 62), January, 2011 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Well wishes (13 of 62), January, 2011 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Well wishes (14 of 62), January, 2011 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Well wishes (15 of 62), January, 2011 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Well wishes (16 of 62), January, 2011 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Well wishes (17 of 62), January, 2011 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Well wishes (18 of 62), January, 2011 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Well wishes (19 of 62), January, 2011 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Well wishes (20 of 62), January, 2011 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Well wishes (21 of 62), January, 2011 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Well wishes (22 of 62), January, 2011 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Well wishes (23 of 62), January, 2011 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Well wishes (24 of 62), January, 2011 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Well wishes (25 of 62), January, 2011 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Well wishes (26 of 62), January, 2011 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Well wishes (27 of 62), January, 2011 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Well wishes (28 of 62), January, 2011 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Well wishes (29 of 62), January, 2011 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Well wishes (30 of 62), January, 2011 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Well wishes (31 of 62), January, 2011 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Well wishes (32 of 62), January, 2011 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Well wishes (33 of 62), January, 2011 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Well wishes (34 of 62), January, 2011 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Well wishes (35 of 62), January, 2011 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Well wishes (36 of 62), January, 2011 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Well wishes (37 of 62), January, 2011 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Well wishes (38 of 62), January, 2011 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Well wishes (39 of 62), January, 2011 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Well wishes (40 of 62), January, 2011 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Well wishes (41 of 62), January, 2011 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Well wishes (42 of 62), January, 2011 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Well wishes (43 of 62), January, 2011 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Well wishes (44 of 62), January, 2011 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Well wishes (45 of 62), January, 2011 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Well wishes (46 of 62), January, 2011 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Well wishes (47 of 62), January, 2011 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Well wishes (48 of 62), January, 2011 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Well wishes (49 of 62), January, 2011 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Well wishes (50 of 62), January, 2011 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Well wishes (51 of 62), January, 2011 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Well wishes (52 of 62), January, 2011 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Well wishes (53 of 62), January, 2011 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Well wishes (54 of 62), January, 2011 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Well wishes (55 of 62), January, 2011 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Well wishes (56 of 62), January, 2011 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Well wishes (57 of 62), January, 2011 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Well wishes (58 of 62), January, 2011 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Well wishes (59 of 62), January, 2011 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Well wishes (60 of 62), January, 2011 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Well wishes (61 of 62), January, 2011 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Well wishes (62 of 62), January, 2011 (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Well wishes (1 of 18), February, 2011 (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - Well wishes (2 of 18), February, 2011 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Well wishes (3 of 18), February, 2011 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Well wishes (4 of 18), February, 2011 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Well wishes (5 of 18), February, 2011 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Well wishes (6 of 18), February, 2011 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Well wishes (7 of 18), February, 2011 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Well wishes (8 of 18), February, 2011 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Well wishes (9 of 18), February, 2011 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Well wishes (10 of 18), February, 2011 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Well wishes (11 of 18), February, 2011 (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Well wishes (12 of 18), February, 2011 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Well wishes (13 of 18), February, 2011 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Well wishes (14 of 18), February, 2011 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Well wishes (15 of 18), February, 2011 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Well wishes (16 of 18), February, 2011 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Well wishes (17 of 18), February, 2011 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Well wishes (18 of 18), February, 2011 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Well wishes (1 of 6), March, 2011 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Well wishes (2 of 6), March, 2011 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Well wishes (3 of 6), March, 2011 (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Well wishes (4 of 6), March, 2011 (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Well wishes (5 of 6), March, 2011 (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - Well wishes (6 of 6), March, 2011 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Well wishes (1 of 2), April, 2011 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Well wishes (2 of 2), April, 2011 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Well wishes, May, 2011 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Well wishes (1 of 2), June, 2011 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Well wishes (2 of 2), June, 2011 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Well wishes (1 of 2), July, 2011-December, 2011 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Well wishes (1 of 2), July, 2011-December, 2011 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Well wishes, January, 2012-April, 2012 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Well wishes from public figures (1 of 4), January, 2011 (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Well wishes from public figures (2 of 4), January, 2011 (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - Well wishes from public figures (3 of 4), January, 2011 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Well wishes from public figures (4 of 4), January, 2011 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Well wishes from public figures, February, 2011-August, 2011 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Well wishes from public figures, 2012 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Well wishes, office inventory (1 of 2), 2011-2012 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Well wishes, office inventory (2 of 2), 2011-2012 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Cards for other victims, 2011 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Cards for other victims- Gabriel Zimmerman, 2011 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Series 2: Press Clippings, 2011-2012
    This series contains clippings related to the shooting, Giffords recovery, her return to Congress and her resignation.
    - (1 of 5), January 9, 2011-January 15, 2011 (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - (2 of 5), January 9, 2011-January 15, 2011 (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - (3 of 5), January 9, 2011-January 15, 2011 (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - (4 of 5), January 9, 2011-January 15, 2011 (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - (5 of 5), January 9, 2011-January 15, 2011 (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - (1 of 2), January 16, 2011-January 22, 2011 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - (2 of 2), January 16, 2011-January 22, 2011 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - (1 of 2), January 23, 2011-January 31, 2011 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - (2 of 2), January 23, 2011-January 31, 2011 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - February 1, 2011-February 21, 2011 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - March 8, 2011-March 29, 2011 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - April 15, 2011-April 30, 2011 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - May, 2011 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - June 13, 2011-June 16, 2011 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - (1 of 2), August 2, 2011-August 5, 2011 (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - (2 of 2), August 2, 2011-August 5, 2011 (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - October, 2011 (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - November, 2011 (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - December, 2011 (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - January 9, 2012 (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - January 23, 2012 (Box 60, Folder 16)
    - January 24, 2012-January 26, 2012 (Box 60, Folder 17)
    - April, 2012 (Box 60, Folder 18)
  - Series 3: Audio visual materials, 2011-2012
    This series contains a CD of photographs and DVDs of programs related to the shooting.
    - Tragedy and Transcendance in Tucson, 2011 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Together We Thrive: Tucson & America, Arizona Public Media, 2011 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Stand Up to Stop Violence featuring David Fitzsimmons, Emcee Elliot Glicksman, Tom Potter, Gary Hood, Suzie Sexton, Michael Hurley, Joey Giron and Butch Lord, May 1, 2011 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Together We Heal, Arizona Public Media, 2012 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Series 4: Memorabilia, 2010-2012
    This series contains memorabilia related to the shooting including well-wishing and sign in books from congress, flags and proclamations and resolutions.
    - Billboard mock-up, March 19, 2011 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Book: Congressional well wishes (1 of 6), undated (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Book: Congressional well wishes (2 of 6), undated (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Book: Congressional well wishes (3 of 6), undated (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Book: Congressional well wishes (4 of 6), undated (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Book: Congressional well wishes (5 of 6), undated (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Book: Congressional well wishes (6 of 6), undated (Box 62, Folder 7)